횞혬횞혩횞혨횞혲횞혶 횞혵횞짠횞혮횞혷횞혫횞혲횞징횞혱횞혮횞짢! 횞혬횞짝횞혮횞혮횞짧 횞혬횞짠횞혮횞혷횞혫횞혲횞징횞혱횞혮횞짢 횞혬횞짧횞혪횞혩횞짤 횞혩횞혯횞혷횞혺 횞혬횞혨횞혰횞짢횞혮횞혺.
횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮 횞혨횞혮횞혴횞혵횞혲횞혶 횞혩횞혲횞혰횞혫,
횞혷횞짧횞짠횞혵횞혰횞혲횞혶 횞혩횞혲횞혰횞혫 횞혮횞혲횞짤횞혻횞혲횞혶 횞혩횞혲횞혰횞혫.
횞짠횞혮횞혷횞혫횞혲횞징횞혱횞혮횞짢, 횞혷횞혲횞혫 횞혨횞혰횞짢횞혲 횞혬횞짚횞짢횞징횞혮횞혷횞혮횞짧.
횞혴횞혵 횞혨횞혰횞혫 횞혴횞혨횞혺 횞혷횞혨횞혲횞짧횞혻횞혮 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞짤횞혮횞혮횞혬 횞혩횞혲횞혺 횞짤횞혮횞혮횞혲횞혶.
횞혨횞혲횞짧횞혲!
횞짤횞혱횞혮횞짙 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혴횞혵횞혲횞혶!
횞짧횞혩횞혲횞혨 횞짠횞짚횞혬!
횞짧횞짖횞짤횞혬 횞징횞짚횞혮횞혪'횞혬!
횞혷횞혲횞혫 횞혨횞혰횞짢횞혲 횞혬횞짚횞짢횞징횞혮횞혷횞혮횞짧.
횞혩횞혩횞짠횞짤횞혬. 횞혨횞혲횞혳 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혷횞혪횞혲횞짖 횞혷횞혴횞혨횞혺 횞혵횞혯'횞혩횞혮횞혱횞혲횞혻횞징횞짠횞혲?
횞혯횞혬 횞혷횞혨횞혮횞혫 횞짚횞짤횞혮횞혱. 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짢횞혮횞혨횞혬 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞짢횞혷횞혯횞혮횞짢 횞짤횞혶 횞혩횞짠횞짝횞혬 횞혬횞짢횞혰횞혮횞혩?
횞혴횞혺. 횞혩횞짢횞혷횞혯횞혮횞짢 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혻횞혴횞혻횞징 횞혲횞혷횞혲횞혻횞혮.
횞혩횞짢횞혷횞혯횞혮횞짢 횞혲횞혷횞혲횞혻횞혬, 횞짧횞혮횞혫횞혬 횞짢횞혩횞혬 횞혵횞혳. 횞혩횞혲횞혲. 횞혷횞혬 횞혯횞혬 횞혬횞혲횞혬?
횞혷횞혬 횞혯횞혬 횞혬횞짤횞혱횞혮횞짧 횞혬횞혯횞혨횞짧? 횞짤횞혨횞혵횞짧 횞혨횞혲횞혳 횞혯횞혬 횞혵횞혬횞혪횞혲횞짖 횞혵횞혯'횞혩횞혮횞혱횞혲횞혻횞징횞짠횞혲. 횞혴횞혺, 횞혯횞혬 횞혷횞혬 횞짤횞짢횞혮횞짝횞혬 횞혵... 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혷횞징횞혩횞혲횞짢 횞혵횞혳, 횞혯횞혬 횞혷횞혨횞혮횞혫 횞짚횞짤횞혮횞혱. 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짢횞혮횞혨횞혬? 횞혴횞혺. 횞혲횞짤횞짢 횞혩횞짢횞혻횞혯횞혮횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞혲횞혷횞혲횞혻횞혬 횞짠횞혱횞혺. 횞혲횞짤횞짢 횞혩횞혲횞혷횞혲횞혻횞혬, 횞짧횞혮횞혫횞혬 횞짢횞혩횞혬. 횞혩횞혲횞혲. 횞혩횞혮횞혨횞혻횞혬, 횞짧횞혪횞혲횞혫, 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짖횞혮횞짤횞혬 횞짝횞혰횞혮횞짠?
횞혷횞혬 횞혬횞짖횞혻횞혲횞혲횞혺? 횞혷횞혬 횞혯횞혬 횞혬횞짤횞혱횞혮횞짧 횞혬횞혯횞혨횞짧? 횞짤횞혮횞혨횞혵횞짧 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혳 횞혨횞혲횞혳 횞혷횞혪횞혲횞짖횞혲횞혶, 횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혷횞혻횞혮횞짚횞짙 횞혩횞혲횞혫횞혲횞혲횞혶? 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혷횞징횞혩횞혲횞짢 횞혵횞혳, 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짤횞혮횞혨횞혵, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혷횞징횞혩횞혲횞짢. 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혻횞혮횞징횞짖 횞혲횞짤횞짢, 횞혬횞혻횞혬 횞혬횞짢횞혻횞혯횞혮횞짢횞혲횞혶. 횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혷횞혻횞혮횞짚횞짙 횞혩횞혲횞혫횞혲횞혲횞혶? 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혷횞혩횞짠횞짤 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혳 횞혵횞혬횞혲횞짢횞혪횞짖, 횞혨횞혻횞혲
횞혷횞혬 횞혬횞짖횞혻횞혲횞혲횞혺? 횞혷횞혬 횞혯횞혬 횞혬횞짤횞혱횞혮횞짧 횞혬횞혯횞혨횞짧? 횞짤횞혮횞혨횞혵횞짧 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혳 횞혨횞혲횞혳 횞혷횞혪횞혲횞짖횞혲횞혶, 횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혷횞혻횞혮횞짚횞짙 횞혩횞혲횞혫횞혲횞혲횞혶? 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혷횞징횞혩횞혲횞짢 횞혵횞혳, 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짤횞혮횞혨횞혵, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혷횞징횞혩횞혲횞짢. 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혻횞혮횞징횞짖 횞혲횞짤횞짢. 횞혨횞혯 횞짧횞징횞혩횞혲횞짢 횞혴횞혷횞혮 횞혩횞혺 횞혨횞혫횞혶, 횞짧횞징횞혩횞혲횞짢 횞혵횞혲 횞혨횞혲횞혳 횞혷횞혪횞혲횞짖횞혲횞혶, 횞혨횞혵 횞짧횞혲횞짧횞혺 횞혵횞혲 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혯횞혬. 횞혬횞혻횞혬 횞혬횞짢횞혻횞혯횞혮횞짢횞혲횞혶. 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혷횞혩횞짠횞짤 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혳 횞혵횞혬횞혲횞짢횞혪횞짖, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혷횞징횞혩횞혲횞짢 횞혵횞혳. 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짢횞혮횞혨횞혬 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞짢횞혻횞혯횞혮횞짢횞혲횞혶? 횞혴횞혺. 횞혩횞짢횞혻횞혯횞혮횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞혲횞혷횞혲횞혻횞혬. 횞짧횞혮횞혫횞혬 횞짢횞혩횞혬. 횞혩횞혩횞짠횞짤횞혬. 횞혩횞혮횞혨횞혻횞혬 횞짧횞혪횞혲횞혫, 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짖횞혮횞짤횞혬 횞짝횞혰횞혮횞짠? 횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혷횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞혲횞혫횞혲횞혲횞혶? 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짢횞혮횞짝횞혬 횞짤횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혨횞혴횞혻횞징 횞혵횞혳 횞짚횞혬, 횞혨횞혴횞혻횞징 횞혵횞혳 횞혩횞짢횞혨횞짤? 횞혷횞혬 횞혬횞짤횞혱횞혮횞짧 횞혬횞혯횞혨횞짧? 횞혷횞혲 횞혷횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞혲횞혫횞혲횞혲횞혶? 횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혻횞혩횞혮횞짠? 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞짤
횞혬횞혫횞짚횞짠횞혱 횞혬횞혯횞혬, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞짤횞혮횞혨횞혵 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혶 횞혩횞짧횞혷횞혲횞혷횞혮횞짧, 횞혩횞짧횞혮횞혶 횞혵횞혩, 횞혨횞혲횞혳 횞혷횞혪횞혲횞짖횞혲횞혶 횞혵횞혯'횞혩횞혮횞혱횞혲횞혻횞징횞짠횞혲? 횞혨횞혯 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짚횞짤횞혮횞혱 횞혬횞혮횞혵횞혳 횞혲횞짤횞짢, 횞혮횞짤횞혷횞혬 횞혲횞혷횞혲횞혻횞혬. 횞짧횞혮횞혫횞혬, 횞혻횞징횞짧횞혫횞짢 횞짢횞혮횞혩. 횞혩횞혩횞짠횞짤횞혬, 횞짧횞혮횞혫횞혬 횞짢횞혩횞혬 횞혵횞혳.
횞혩횞혮횞혨'횞혻횞혬, 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짖횞혮횞짤횞혬 횞짝횞혰횞혮횞짠. 횞혷횞혬? 횞혷횞혬 횞혯횞혬 횞혬횞혫횞혩횞짢 횞혬횞혯횞혬?
횞혷횞혬 횞혪횞혶 횞혨횞짧횞혬? 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짤횞혮횞혨횞혵 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞짤횞혨횞혵횞혬. 횞혪횞혶 횞혩횞혷횞짤횞혱횞짢횞혬, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞짢횞짝횞혲횞짧횞혲 횞혵횞혯'횞혩횞혮횞혱횞혲횞혻횞징횞짠횞혲.
횞혩횞혩횞짠횞짤횞혬. 횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혶 횞혷횞짢횞혲횞혷횞혲횞혶 횞혲횞혫횞혲횞혲횞혶? 횞혷횞혬 횞혯횞혬? 횞혻횞짤횞혰횞짠? 횞혷횞혬 횞혯횞혬 횞혬횞혫횞혩횞짢 횞혬횞혯횞혬?
횞혨횞짧횞혶 횞혲횞짤횞짢, 횞혲횞짤횞짢 횞혩횞혲횞혷횞혲횞혻횞혬, 횞혯횞혬 횞혬횞혴횞혮횞혵.
횞짧횞혮횞혫횞혬. 횞혩횞혩횞짠횞짤횞혬. 횞징횞혵횞혲횞혰횞혬, 횞짖횞혯횞혩횞혮 횞혬횞혴횞혮횞혵, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혷횞혬횞짢횞짝횞혵, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혲횞혮횞혫횞짖 횞혵횞혬횞징횞짧횞혫횞짢. 횞혨횞혲횞혳 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혷횞혪횞혲횞짖 횞혵횞혴횞혵 횞혰횞혮횞혩 횞혬횞짢횞짝횞혵?
횞혬횞짢횞짝횞혵 횞혯횞혬 횞혲횞혮횞짧횞짢 횞짚횞짤횞혮횞혱, 횞짧횞징횞혩횞혲횞짢, 횞혬횞짢횞짝횞혵 횞혯횞혬 횞혬횞혬횞혲횞혨 횞혩횞혴횞혲횞혴횞짢. 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짖횞혮횞혩횞짢 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혴횞혲횞혴횞짢 횞혮횞혻횞혴횞혻횞징 횞혲횞혷횞혲횞혻횞혬 횞혩횞징횞혷횞혱횞혬.
횞혬횞혩횞혻횞짧 횞혨횞혮 횞짤횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짢횞혮횞짝횞혬 횞짤횞혪횞혶 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혨횞징횞혩횞혲횞짢 횞혵횞혳 횞혨횞혲횞짚횞혬 횞혯횞혬 횞혬횞짢횞짝횞혵?
횞짧횞혮횞혫횞혬.
횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혷횞혨횞혵횞혻횞혩횞혲, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혲횞혮횞혫횞짖 횞혵횞혬횞징횞짧횞혫횞짢. 횞짢횞짠 횞짧횞혪횞혲횞혫횞혮 횞혵횞혲 횞혨횞혲횞혳 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혷횞혪횞혲횞짖 횞혵횞혨횞혵횞혻횞혩횞혲.
횞혨횞혵횞혻횞혩횞혲 횞혯횞혬 횞짚횞혲횞짝횞혮횞짜 횞혩횞혮횞혪횞혩횞혮횞혻횞혲횞혶? 횞짢횞징횞혲횞혬 횞혨횞혮횞혵횞혲? 횞짢횞징횞혲횞혬, 횞짢횞징횞혲횞혬, 횞짢횞징횞혲횞혬, 횞짢횞징횞혲횞혬. 횞짢횞혪횞짖, 횞혨횞혵횞혻횞혩횞혲 횞혯횞혬 횞짢횞징횞혲횞혬. 횞짢횞혪횞짖, 횞혨횞혵횞혻횞혩횞혲 횞혯횞혬 횞짢횞징횞혲횞혬. 횞혨횞혵횞혻횞혩횞혲 횞혯횞혬 횞짢횞징횞혲횞혬. 횞혨횞혵횞혵횞혬, 횞혨횞혲횞혳 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혲횞혮횞혫횞짖, 횞혩횞혮횞혨 횞혻횞징횞혩횞혲횞짢 횞혵횞혳, 횞혨횞혵횞혵횞혬. 횞짖횞짢횞혩 횞혱횞혮횞혩.
횞짤횞혮횞혩 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮 횞혩횞혷횞혫횞짢횞혲횞혳 횞혴횞혲횞짝횞혫 횞혻횞짧횞혻횞혬횞혪 횞혬횞혻횞혴횞혮횞혺,
횞혮횞혬횞짚횞짖횞혶 횞혴횞혲횞짝횞혫 횞혻횞짖횞혩횞혮횞짢 횞혨횞짧 횞짧횞짠횞혮횞짚횞짧 횞혬횞혷횞혩횞혰횞혻횞혲횞혶 횞혩횞짤횞혵횞혮횞혶.
횞짢횞혨횞짤횞혲횞짧,
횞짖횞혵횞혲횞혳 횞혵횞짤횞혷횞혮횞짢 횞짖횞혵 횞혲횞혰횞징횞혲 횞혲횞혫횞혲횞혫횞혮횞짧 횞혩횞혲횞혻횞혳 횞혮횞혩횞혲횞혺 횞혬횞혷횞혮횞짢횞혬.
횞혩횞혬횞짝횞혵횞혰횞혬, 횞혰횞혷횞혮횞혫.
횞혩횞혬횞짝횞혵횞혰횞혬. 횞혩횞징횞혮횞짙. 횞혩횞혬횞짝횞혵횞혰횞혬. 횞혩횞혮횞짠횞짢 횞혱횞혮횞혩, 횞혬횞혷횞혮횞짢횞혬. 횞혷횞혬 횞짤횞혵횞혮횞혷횞혳?
횞짧횞혮횞혫횞혬. 횞혷횞짢횞혪횞혲횞짤횞혬 횞혱횞혮횞혩. 횞혲횞혮횞짚횞혲 횞짤횞혵 횞짤횞혷횞혵횞혬, 횞혷횞짧횞혨횞혲횞혶 횞혵횞혳 횞혪횞혶 횞혵횞짝횞짖횞혲횞짙. 횞짝횞짖횞혲횞짙 횞혨횞혲횞혯횞혬 횞혷횞혪횞혻횞혲횞혩, 횞짤횞혲횞혪횞짖횞혮횞혺. 횞짧횞혮횞혫횞혬, 횞짧횞혮횞혫횞혬, 횞짧횞혮횞혫횞혬. 횞혯횞혬 횞혷횞혨횞혮횞혫 횞짠횞혮횞혵 횞혩횞혨횞짢횞짝횞혮횞짧 횞혬횞혩횞짢횞혲횞짧. 횞혲횞혮횞짚횞혲. 횞짠횞혫횞혲횞혷횞혬, 횞혵횞혷횞혩횞혰횞혺. 횞혨횞혬, 횞혷횞혮횞짢횞혬, 횞혨횞혲횞혯횞혬 횞혴횞짧횞혩 횞혲횞짚횞혬. 횞혲횞짚횞혬 횞혬횞혴횞짧횞혩 횞짤횞혵횞혳. 횞혯횞혬 횞혵횞혨 횞혬횞혴횞짧횞혩 횞짤횞혵횞혲, 횞혯횞혨횞짧 횞혷횞혴횞혮횞혻횞짧 횞혴횞짧횞혲횞혩횞혬, 횞혫횞혩횞혲.
횞혩횞혬횞짝횞혵횞혰횞혬. 횞짠횞혫횞혲횞혷횞혬. 횞짧횞혮횞혫횞혬 횞짢횞혩횞혬, 횞혷횞혮횞짢횞혬. 횞혲횞혫횞혲횞혫횞혮횞짧 횞혬횞혲횞혨 횞혫횞혩횞짢 횞혻횞짚횞혵횞혨, 횞혨횞혳 횞혨횞혵 횞짧횞혪횞혯횞혲횞혶. 횞혩횞혬횞짝횞혵횞혰횞혬 횞혪횞혶 횞혵횞혳. 횞혩횞혮횞짠횞짢 횞혨횞혮횞짢, 횞혷횞혮횞짢횞혬, 횞혬횞짢횞혨횞짤횞혲 횞혵횞혲 횞혵횞짧횞짧 횞혵횞혳 횞짧횞짚횞혮횞혰, 횞혩횞혩횞짠횞짤횞혬. 횞짧횞짚횞혮횞혰 횞혷횞짝횞혮횞혲횞혺. 횞징횞혩횞혩횞혬. 횞혯횞혬 횞혱횞혮횞혩 횞혵횞짚
횞혩횞혬횞짝횞혵횞혰횞혬, 횞짠횞혫횞혲횞혷횞혬. 횞짧횞혮횞혫횞혬 횞짢횞혩횞혬 횞혷횞혮횞짢횞혬. 횞혲횞혫횞혲횞혫횞혮횞짧 횞혬횞혲횞혨 횞혫횞혩횞짢 횞혻횞짚횞혵횞혨, 횞혨횞혳 횞혨횞혵 횞짧횞혪횞혯횞혲횞혶. 횞혩횞혬횞짝횞혵횞혰횞혬 횞혪횞혶 횞혵횞혳. 횞혩횞혮횞짠횞짢 횞짢횞혮횞혩, 횞혷횞혮횞짢횞혬, 횞혬횞짢횞짤횞혬 횞혵횞혲 횞혵횞짧횞짧 횞혵횞혳 횞짧횞짚횞혮횞혰 횞혩횞혩횞짠횞짤횞혬? 횞짧횞짚횞혮횞혰 횞혷횞짝횞혮횞혲횞혺. 횞징횞혩횞혩횞혬. 횞혯횞혬 횞혱횞혮횞혩 횞혵횞짚횞혻횞혲 횞혰횞혩횞짢횞짧 횞혬횞혷횞혩횞혰횞혺. 횞짢횞혪횞짖, 횞혷횞혮횞짢횞혬, 횞혲횞짤 횞혵횞혲 횞혪횞혶 횞혩횞짤횞혩횞혲횞혵횞혳 횞짚횞짢횞혰횞혲횞혶. 횞짤횞혮횞짤횞혻횞혲횞혶, 횞짧횞짢횞혲횞혰횞혲 횞혨횞혲횞혯횞혬 횞혲횞혮횞짚횞혲. 횞혵횞혨 횞혻횞혮횞짢횞혨, 횞혮횞짢횞혫횞혲횞혶 횞혪횞혶 횞짤횞혶. 횞혪횞혶 횞짠횞혮횞혷횞짚횞짠 횞혫횞혲횞징횞짠, 횞혵횞혨횞혮횞혱횞혮, 횞짤횞혲횞혪횞짖횞혮횞혺, 횞짧횞혨횞혷횞혲횞혻횞혲 횞혵횞혷횞혰횞혲횞짢 횞혷횞혩횞짝횞짖. 횞혷횞짝횞혩횞혲횞짖횞혲, 횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짖횞혮횞짤횞혬 횞혩횞혫횞혲횞혮횞짠? 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혰횞혮횞짤횞혩 횞짤횞짖횞혮횞짧. 횞혬횞혷횞혮횞짢횞혬, 횞혷횞짠횞짢횞짢, 횞혪횞혫횞혮횞혵. 횞짖횞짤횞짢 횞짤횞혵 횞혷횞혮횞짢횞혬, 횞짤횞혲횞혪횞짖횞혮횞혺 횞혨횞짧
횞혬횞짚횞짧횞짠횞혲횞혶, 횞혲횞짤횞짧횞혫횞혵 횞혵횞혬횞징횞혮횞혮횞짧 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혶 횞혩횞혰횞혮횞혴횞혷횞혬.
횞혬횞혷횞혮횞짢횞혬, 횞혩횞혮횞짠횞짢 횞혨횞혮횞짢, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혷횞혮횞혴횞혺 횞짚횞혲횞짠횞징.
횞혬횞혷횞혮횞짢횞혬 횞짤횞혲횞짤 횞혵횞혳 횞혲횞혮횞짚횞혲 횞짤횞혵 횞혰횞혮횞혵횞짝횞혬,
횞혴횞혫횞혨횞혲 횞짤횞짧횞짤횞혵횞혰 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혬 횞혵횞혻횞혲횞혰횞혮횞혲 횞혲횞혩횞짤.
횞혬횞혷횞혮횞짢횞혬, 횞혯횞혬 횞짠횞혮횞짢횞혫횞짢횞혮횞혲, 횞혱횞혵횞혨횞혲횞혶, 횞혯횞혬 횞혷횞혬 횞짤횞혬횞혮횞혵횞혳 횞혬횞혲횞혮횞혶.
횞혬횞짧횞혲횞혲횞짖횞짝횞혮횞짧 횞혩횞혯횞혷횞혺 횞혬횞혷횞혩횞혰횞혺 횞혬횞혲횞혨 횞혴횞혷횞혮횞혩횞혺 횞혨횞징횞혮횞짢횞혬.
횞혷횞짝횞혫 횞짤횞혻횞혲, 횞혨횞혶 횞혬횞혰횞혵횞혱횞짧 횞혵횞짖횞짤횞혮횞짧 횞혯횞혨횞짧, 횞짖횞짤횞혬 횞혯횞혨횞짧 횞혩횞혫횞혲횞징횞짠횞짢횞혱횞혲횞혮횞짧.
횞혨횞혬, 횞혲횞혮횞짤횞짢, 횞짧횞짤횞혮횞혷횞혬 횞짤횞짢횞혨횞짤, 횞짧횞짤횞혮횞혷횞혬 횞짤횞짢횞혨횞짤.
횞혨횞혷횞짝횞짖횞혲횞혶 횞혱횞혴횞혻횞혮횞혵횞혮횞혪횞혲횞혲횞혶 횞혷횞짧횞혮횞혰횞혴횞혷횞혲횞혶 횞짖횞짤횞혮횞혲횞혲횞혶 횞혵횞짖횞혯횞혮횞짢,
횞혨횞혳 횞혬횞짤횞짧횞혫횞혵 횞혵횞혬횞징횞혮횞혮횞짧 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혶 횞혬횞혲횞혱횞혩.
횞혨횞혷횞혨, 횞혴횞혺, 횞짧횞짤횞혷횞짖횞혲, 횞혩횞혷횞혪횞혲횞짢횞혬 횞짤횞혵횞혲 횞혵횞혷횞혱횞혬 횞혲횞짤 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞징횞짚횞짢 횞혬횞혲횞징횞혱횞혮횞짢횞혲횞혬.
횞짧횞짚횞짧횞혰횞혲 횞짤횞혶 횞짖횞혷횞혮횞혫 50. 횞혴횞혺, 횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞혷횞짢 횞짖횞혫횞혬 횞혪횞혮횞짢횞혫횞혮횞혺 횞혵횞혰횞혩횞짢'횞혬 횞혷횞혬횞징횞혮횞혴횞혻횞혮횞짧?
횞혷횞혬 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞혨횞혷횞짢? 횞혴횞짧횞혮횞혩 횞짤횞혶: "횞혵횞혨 횞혴횞혷횞짖횞혫횞혮 횞혩횞혨횞짤횞짢".
횞혵횞혲 횞혨횞혷횞혨 횞혲횞짤 횞혵횞혲 횞혷횞혷횞짧횞혲횞혻횞혬.
횞혨횞혶 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짤횞혮횞혵횞혱 횞혩횞혰횞혮횞혷횞짢 횞혬횞혻횞혵횞혷횞혫,
횞혬횞혲횞혬 횞혰횞혩횞짢 횞혩횞짤횞짖횞짧 횞짤횞짢횞혬.
횞혷횞혬?
횞짧횞짤횞혮횞혩횞혬 횞혨횞짢횞혩횞짖, 횞혨횞혲횞짧횞혲.
횞혬횞혻횞혬, 횞짧횞짤횞혮횞혩횞혬 횞혨횞짢횞혩횞짖.
횞혬횞혶 횞혵횞혨 횞짢횞짝횞혮 횞혵횞혩횞혮횞혨 횞혩횞혪횞혵횞혵 횞혬횞혨횞혲횞혫횞혲횞혨횞혮횞혵횞혮횞혪횞혲횞혬,
횞짤횞혬횞혲횞혲횞짧횞혬 횞짤횞혮횞혻횞혬 횞혷횞짤횞혵 횞혬횞짖횞짢횞혩횞혲횞혶 횞짤횞짤횞혵횞혱횞혮 횞혴횞혨횞혺.
횞혰횞혴횞혷횞혫 횞혵횞징횞혲횞혲횞혶 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혷횞혩횞혰횞혺 횞혩횞짧횞혮횞혶 횞혬횞혯횞혷횞혺 횞짤횞혬횞혮횞짠횞짝횞혩 횞혵횞혴횞혳.
횞짧횞짚횞짖횞혲 횞혨횞혵횞혲횞혲 횞혩횞혩횞짠횞짤횞혬, 횞혵횞혬횞혻횞혲횞혰 횞혨횞짧 횞혷횞혩횞혻횞혮횞짧.
횞혷횞혩횞혰횞혺 횞짤횞혱횞혮횞짧횞혲, 횞짚횞혲횞징 횞혨횞혮횞짙 횞짠횞혲횞혲횞짠, 횞짧횞혨횞혷횞혲횞혺 횞혵횞혲. 횞혨횞혲횞혯횞혬 횞짤횞혨횞혵횞혮횞짧, 횞짖횞혫횞혬 횞혪횞혮횞짢횞혫횞혮횞혺, 횞혲횞혫횞짖횞짧횞혲 횞혬횞혴횞혮횞혵, 횞징횞혲횞짢횞짠횞혵, 횞혨횞혲횞혺 횞혵횞혲 횞짤횞혮횞혶 횞혩횞짖횞혲횞혬. 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혲횞혮횞혫횞짖 횞혴횞혷횞혬 횞징횞짚횞짢횞혲 횞혬횞혲횞징횞혱횞혮횞짢횞혲횞혬 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞짠횞짢횞혨횞짧횞혲? 횞혮횞혮횞혨횞혵횞혬, 횞짚횞혲횞징 횞혨횞혮횞짙 횞짠횞혲횞혲횞짠. 횞징횞혵횞혲횞혰횞혬 횞혨횞혫횞혮횞혻횞혲, 횞혬횞혷횞혩횞혰횞혺 횞혩횞혷횞짧횞혷횞혱횞혲횞짠횞혬 횞혬횞징횞짧횞혲횞혲횞혶. 횞혵횞혨!
횞혷횞혬 횞짧횞짠횞짢횞혨? 횞혩횞혮횞혮횞혫횞혨횞혲.
횞혬횞혷횞혮횞짢횞혬, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞짖횞혻횞혲횞짧횞혲 횞혵횞혳 횞짢횞혮횞혩 횞짚횞혬 횞혩횞혬횞혲횞징횞혱횞혮횞짢횞혲횞혬,
횞혨횞짧 횞혲횞혮횞혫횞짖횞짧, 횞혲횞혫횞짖 횞혴횞혵횞혵횞혲, 횞혨횞혩횞혵 횞짧횞짢횞혨횞혲 횞혯횞혬 횞짚횞짤횞혮횞혱: 횞짤횞혮횞짢횞짤 횞짤횞혵 17. 횞혬횞짢횞짝횞혵. 횞짤횞혮횞혮횞혬 횞혬횞짢횞짝횞혵. 횞혬횞혷횞혮횞짢횞혬, 횞짚횞혲횞징 횞혨횞짙 횞짠횞혲횞혲. 횞짧횞혺, 횞짧횞혺. 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혮 횞혫횞혩횞짢, 횞짧횞혰횞짤횞혩횞혲 횞징횞혲횞혪횞혵횞징. 횞혻횞혲횞징횞혲횞혲횞혺 횞혩횞혮횞혮횞짖횞혫횞짧 횞혴횞혲횞징횞혮횞혲, 횞혱횞혮횞혩? 횞혮횞혵횞징횞혲횞혴횞혮횞혶,
횞혩횞짚횞짖횞혶 횞혬횞혩횞혨횞혬 횞짤횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혬횞혮횞혵횞혳 횞혵횞혩횞혲횞짧 횞징횞짚횞짢,
횞짖횞혫횞혲횞짙 횞짤횞짧횞혵횞혳 횞혵횞짚횞혻횞혲횞혷횞혲횞혲횞혬 횞짝횞혩횞혨횞혲횞짧.
횞혯횞혬 횞혬횞혴횞혵 횞혵횞혲횞혵횞혬 횞혱횞혮횞혩 횞혮횞혬횞혷횞짤횞혳 횞짝횞짚횞혲횞혲횞혬.
횞혨횞혮, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혷횞혷횞혬횞짢.
횞혰횞혩횞혮횞짢횞짧 횞혬횞짠횞혮횞혷횞혫횞혲횞징횞혱횞혮횞짢횞혲횞짧 횞짧횞짤횞혮횞혩 횞혩횞짤횞혩횞혮횞짖 횞혬횞혩횞혨. 횞혯횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬, 횞혩횞혱횞혵횞짖횞혫.
횞짢횞짠 횞혷횞짧횞혰횞혲횞혵, 횞짢횞짠 횞혷횞짧횞혰횞혲횞혵, 횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧 횞혨횞혮횞혷횞짢횞짧 횞혻횞혪횞혷횞짢? 횞혨횞혮횞짚횞징, 횞혻횞혮횞짢횞혨 횞혷횞짝횞혱횞짖횞짢횞짧. 횞징횞혵횞혲횞혰횞혬, 횞짧횞혷횞짤횞혲횞혴횞혲.
횞짤횞혷횞짖횞혮횞혺, 횞짧횞혴횞혻횞혲횞징 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혷횞혴횞혮횞혻횞혲횞혮횞짧, 횞혲횞혨횞혵횞혵횞혬, 횞짧횞짤횞혱횞혮횞짙 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혺, 횞짧횞짤횞혲횞혶 횞혵횞혬횞혺, 횞짢횞짠 횞짤횞혲횞짢횞혨횞혮 횞혱횞혮횞혩.
횞혯횞혬 횞혨횞혮횞혱횞혮 횞혪횞혷횞혮횞짢, 횞혨횞혩횞혵 횞혵횞혷횞혴횞혮횞짢 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혮, 횞혨횞혵 횞짧횞혫횞혨횞혪.
횞혲횞혨횞혵횞혵횞혬, 횞짧횞혴횞혲횞혻횞혮 횞혵횞혲 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혷횞혪횞짢횞짤.
횞혴횞혺, 횞혨횞혫횞혮횞혻횞혲, 횞혩횞혩횞짠횞짤횞혬.
횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혷횞혮횞혴횞짢 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혷횞혴횞혮횞혻횞혲횞짧?
횞혨횞혬횞혵횞혺, 횞혷횞혮횞혴횞짢 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혷횞혴횞혮횞혻횞혬, 횞짧횞짢횞혨횞혬 횞혨횞혲횞혯횞혬 횞혨횞혮횞짚횞혲. 횞혲횞짚횞혬, 횞혰횞혫횞짤횞혬, 횞혵횞혨? 횞혰횞혫횞짤횞혬 횞혵횞혪횞혷횞짢횞혲, 횞짧횞짢횞혨횞혬 횞혨횞혲횞혯횞혬 횞짝횞혩횞짖, 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짢횞혨횞혲횞짧 횞혴횞혯횞혬 횞혫횞혩횞짢. 횞혴횞혷횞혬 횞혬횞혲횞혨 횞짤횞혮횞혮횞혬?
50,000. 횞혨횞혲횞혯횞혬 횞혲횞혫? 횞혯횞혬 횞혵횞혨 횞혲횞혫, 횞혯횞혬 횞혬횞혶 횞짖횞짤횞혲횞혻횞혮 횞짖횞징횞짠 횞짖횞혶 횞혨횞혩횞짢횞혲 횞혪횞혵횞혪횞혵횞짝, 횞짤횞혶 횞혬횞혪횞짢횞혵횞짧횞혲 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혬. 횞혨횞혬, 횞혯횞혬 횞혬횞혴횞혲 횞혱횞혮횞혩횞혬.
횞혯횞혬 횞혰횞짢횞혨, 횞혯횞혬 횞혮횞짢횞징횞혬, 횞혵횞혨 횞짧횞혷횞혴횞혮횞짢 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혬 횞짖횞혴횞짤횞혲횞혮. 횞혷횞혬 횞혯횞혬?
횞혨횞혵횞혬, 횞혨횞혲횞혺 횞혵횞혬 횞짤횞혮횞짠, 횞혯횞혬 횞혰횞짢횞혨 횞혨횞혮횞혱횞혮.
횞혬횞혨횞혮횞혱횞혮 횞짖횞짝횞혷횞혮 횞혱횞혮횞혩, 횞혨횞혩횞혵 횞혬횞짤횞혮횞짠 횞혻횞혪횞혷횞짢 횞혩횞혪횞혵횞혵 횞혬횞혷횞혯횞혵 횞짤횞혵 횞혬횞짧횞혮횞혴횞혻횞혲횞짧.
횞짧횞짢횞혨횞혬, 횞혷횞혬 횞짠횞혮횞짢횞혬? 횞혲횞짤 횞짖횞혵횞혲횞혬횞혶 횞혩횞혵횞혨횞혲. 횞혷횞혬 횞혯횞혬 횞혬횞짤횞혱횞혮횞혲횞혮횞짧 횞혬횞혨횞혵횞혬, 횞짧횞혪횞혲횞혫횞혲 횞혵횞혲? 횞혵횞혨, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혨횞징횞혩횞혲횞짢 횞혵횞혳, 횞혬횞혨횞혮횞혱횞혮 횞혬횞혯횞혬 횞혲횞짤 횞혵횞혮 횞혩횞혵횞혨횞혲 횞혪횞혩횞혮횞혬. 횞혨횞혮횞혱횞혮 횞혰횞혫횞짤 횞혵횞혪횞혷횞짢횞혲, 횞혷횞혬 횞혯횞혬 횞혩횞혵횞혨횞혲? 횞혷횞혬 횞혯횞혬? 횞혻횞혴횞혮횞혺, 횞짧횞혩횞혵횞징횞혬 횞혵횞혷횞혴횞혮횞짢 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혬, 횞혩횞혪횞혵횞혵 횞혯횞혬 횞혩횞혨횞짧 횞혨횞혵횞혲횞혲. 횞혻횞혴횞혮횞혺. 횞짖횞혴횞짤횞혲횞혮, 횞혯횞혬 횞혵횞혨 횞짤횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혵횞혨 횞혷횞혩횞혲횞혺 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞짤횞혮횞짠. 횞짧횞짢횞혨횞혬, 횞혩횞혷횞혴횞혮횞혻횞혲횞혮횞짧 횞혬횞혨횞혵횞혬 횞혲횞짤 횞혵횞혬횞혶 횞혩횞혵횞혨횞혲, 횞혴횞혵 횞혬횞혯횞혲횞짖횞혬 횞혷횞혬횞혴횞혲횞징횞혨횞혮횞짧 횞짤횞혵 횞혬횞혫횞혲횞혲횞혵횞혮횞짧 횞짤횞혻횞혴횞혻횞징횞혮횞짧. 횞짚횞혬 횞혩횞짚횞혻횞혲횞혷횞혬 횞혴횞혵 횞혬횞혨횞혻횞짤횞혲횞혶 횞혻횞혮횞혪횞짖횞혲횞혶, 횞짤횞혮횞짢횞혱횞혲횞혶. 횞혬횞혶 횞짚횞혮횞짧횞혰횞혲횞혶 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혫횞혵횞짧 횞짖횞짤횞짢 횞짚횞짖횞혷횞혲횞혶, 횞혴횞혵 횞혬횞혷횞혻횞혪횞혻횞혮횞혺 횞짤횞혵 횞혬횞혫횞혵횞짧횞혮횞짧 횞짤횞혵 횞혬횞혰횞혵횞혱횞혮횞짧 횞짤횞짠횞혱. 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞짚횞짧횞혰 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혫횞혵횞짧, 횞혩횞혮횞혨횞
횞혯횞혬 횞짝횞혩횞짖 횞혫횞혬횞혮횞혲 횞혵횞혪횞혷횞짢횞혲. 횞혨횞혲횞혯횞혬 횞짤횞혱횞혮횞짧. 횞혯횞혬 횞혨횞혮횞혱횞혮 횞혩횞혵횞혲 횞짤횞혮횞짠, 횞혬횞혷횞혻횞혮횞짖, 횞혨횞혻횞짤횞혲횞혶 횞혷횞혮횞짤횞혴횞혲횞혶. 횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혷횞혩횞혵횞혩횞혵 횞혵횞혲 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혷횞혮횞혰? 횞혩횞혮횞혨횞혻횞혬, 횞혯횞혬 횞혨횞혮횞혱횞혮 횞혰횞혫횞짤 횞혵횞혪횞혷횞짢횞혲. 횞혨횞혯 횞혵횞혷횞혬? 횞혨횞혲횞혳 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혷횞징횞혩횞혲횞짢 횞혨횞짧 횞혯횞혬 횞혴횞짤횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혷횞혻횞징횞혬 횞혵횞혷횞혴횞혮횞짢 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혬 횞짤횞혵횞혮횞짤 횞혰횞혮횞혫횞짤 횞혮횞혵횞혨 횞혷횞짝횞혵횞혲횞혰? 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혷횞혩횞혲횞혺? 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혷횞혮횞혴횞혺 횞혵횞짧횞짧 횞혵횞혳 횞짖횞혴횞짤횞혲횞혮 횞짤횞혵횞혮횞짤 횞혨횞혵횞짙 횞짤횞짠횞혵 횞혩횞짤횞혩횞혲횞혵 횞혬횞짠횞혱횞짖, 횞혩횞짤횞혩횞혲횞혵 횞짤횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혵횞혰횞혮횞짜 횞짖횞혵 횞혬횞혴횞징횞짙. 횞혩횞혮횞혨 횞혻횞징횞혪횞혮횞짢 횞짖횞혻횞혲횞혲횞혺. 횞혷횞혬 횞혯횞혬? 횞짤횞혵횞혮횞짤 횞혨횞혵횞짙 횞짤횞짠횞혵. 횞짤횞혵횞혮횞짤 횞혨횞혵횞짙 횞짤횞짠횞혵. 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혩횞혨횞짧횞혲 횞혩횞혰횞혷횞혲횞짤횞혲횞혶 횞혨횞혵횞짙 횞짤횞짠횞혵 횞짤횞혵횞혮횞짤 횞혨횞혵횞짙. 횞혵횞혨 횞혩횞혱횞혮횞혰. 횞혩횞혮횞혨횞혻횞혬, 횞혩횞혮횞혨횞혻횞혬 횞짤횞혮횞혩. 횞혲횞혮횞혨횞혮.
횞혩횞혮횞혨'횞혻횞혬, 횞혯횞혬 횞혬횞혫횞혰횞혵횞혲횞혵 횞혬횞혯횞혬, 횞혮횞짖횞짤횞혲횞혻횞혮 횞짖횞징횞짠, 횞혯횞혮 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혬 횞짧횞혮횞혴횞혻횞혲횞짧.
횞혯횞혬 횞혬횞혫횞혰횞혵횞혲횞혵! 횞혲횞혨횞혵횞혵횞혬, 횞혩횞혰횞혱횞혲횞혨, 횞혬횞혫횞혰횞혵횞혲횞혵! 횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혷횞징횞짧횞혮횞혩횞혩 횞짖횞혵 횞혬횞징횞혷횞짢횞혱횞혮횞혱 횞혬횞혷횞혱횞혮횞혷횞혱횞혶? 횞혬횞혲횞혲횞짧횞혲 횞혪횞혫횞혮횞혵, 횞혩횞혮횞혨'횞혻횞혬, 횞혯횞혬 횞혬횞혰횞혵횞혮횞혶 횞짤횞혵횞혲. 횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혨횞짖횞짤횞혬? 횞혷횞혬 횞혬횞짤횞혱횞혮횞짧 횞혬횞혯횞혨횞짧? 횞혵횞혨 횞혷횞짧횞혩횞혲횞혲횞짤. 횞혩횞혮횞혨'횞혻횞혬, 횞혯횞혬 횞혬횞혰횞혵횞혮횞혶 횞짤횞혵횞혲, 횞혬횞혰횞혵횞혮횞혶 횞짤횞혵횞혲,
횞짤횞혲횞혬횞혲횞혬 횞혴횞짧횞혮횞혩 횞짖횞혵 횞혬횞혷횞혪횞짢횞짤 횞혩횞혴횞혻횞혲횞징횞혬, 횞혲횞짖횞짠횞혩, 횞혷횞혪횞짢횞짤 횞혷횞혴횞혮횞혻횞혲횞혮횞짧 횞혷횞짤횞혮횞혷횞짤횞혮횞짧 횞짖횞혶 횞혬횞혫횞혰횞혵횞혲횞혶. 횞혨횞혷횞짢 횞혵횞혲, 횞짠횞혰 2,000 횞짤횞짠횞혵, 횞혨횞혷횞짢횞짧횞혲 횞혵횞혮, 횞혮횞혲횞혵횞혮횞혺, 횞혯횞혬 횞혷횞혬 횞짤횞짠횞혲횞혩횞혵횞짧횞혲. 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혲횞혮횞혫횞짖 횞혷횞혬? 횞짠횞혰 20,000 횞짤횞짠횞혵, 횞짧횞짤횞혨횞혲횞짢 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혫횞혰횞혵횞혲횞혵 횞짚횞혬. 횞혨횞혲횞혳 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혩횞짤횞혩횞혲횞혵
횞짤횞혲횞혬횞혲횞혬 횞혴횞짧횞혮횞혩 횞짖횞혵 횞혬횞혷횞혪횞짢횞짤 횞혩횞혴횞혻횞혲횞징횞혬, 횞혲횞짖횞짠횞혩, 횞혷횞혪횞짢횞짤 횞혷횞혴횞혮횞혻횞혲횞혮횞짧 횞혷횞짤횞혮횞혷횞짤횞혮횞짧 횞짖횞혶 횞혬횞혫횞혰횞혵횞혲횞혵. 횞혨횞혷횞짢 횞혵횞혲, 횞짠횞혰 횞혨횞혵횞짚횞혲횞혲횞혶 횞짤횞짠횞혵, 횞혨횞혷횞짢횞짧횞혲 횞혵횞혮, 횞혮횞혨횞혲횞혵횞혮횞혺, 횞혯횞혬 횞혷횞혬 횞짤횞짠횞혲횞혩횞혵횞짧횞혲. 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혲횞혮횞혫횞짖 횞혷횞혬? 횞짠횞혰 횞짖횞짤횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞혨횞혵횞짙 횞짤횞짠횞혵, 횞짧횞짤횞혨횞혲횞짢 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혫횞혰횞혵횞혲횞혵 횞짚횞혬. 횞혨횞혲횞혳 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혩횞짤횞혩횞혲횞혵횞혳? 횞혷횞혬 횞혯횞혬, 횞혷횞혬 횞혯횞혬? 횞짤횞짧횞혮횞짠, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞짖횞혮횞짤횞혬 횞짖횞징횞짠, 횞짤횞짧횞혮횞짠 횞짖횞혴횞짤횞혲횞혮. 횞짖횞짤횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞혨횞혵횞짙 횞짤횞짠횞혵, 횞혴횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬? 횞혵횞혫횞혰횞혵횞혲횞혵 횞혬횞혯횞혬? 횞혴횞혺, 횞짖횞짤횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞혨횞혵횞짙 횞짤횞짠횞혵 횞짖횞혵 횞혬횞혫횞혰횞혵횞혲횞혵, 횞짢횞짠 횞짤횞혲횞혬횞혲횞혬 횞혴횞짧횞혮횞혩 횞짖횞혵 횞혬횞혫횞짢횞혳. 횞혨횞혬, 횞혨횞혩횞혵 횞혨횞혩횞짢횞혲 횞혪횞혵횞혪횞혵횞짝 횞혻횞혪횞짖 횞혩횞혮. 횞짤횞혵횞혮횞짤횞혲횞혶 횞혨횞혵횞짙. 횞혷횞혬? 횞혴횞혺, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혵횞혨 횞혲횞혴횞혮횞혵, 횞혴횞혲 횞짧횞혨횞혮횞짢횞혬 횞혬횞혲횞혲횞짧횞혬 횞짖횞혵횞혲횞혮, 횞혨횞혯 횞혯횞혬
횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혲횞혮횞혫횞짖 횞혷횞혬? 횞혩횞혮횞혨 횞혻횞짖횞짤횞혬 횞혱횞짢횞혲횞혲횞혫 횞혨횞혲횞혺. 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞혬횞혲횞혬 횞혩횞짧횞혮횞혳 횞혬횞혮횞혮횞혲횞혵횞혮횞혺. 횞혩횞혮횞혨 횞혻횞짖횞짤횞혬 횞혱횞짢횞혲횞혲횞혫 횞혨횞혲횞혺. 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짢횞혮횞혨횞혬 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혨횞혮횞혱횞혮 횞혬횞혯횞혬?
횞혯횞혬 횞혬횞혨횞혮횞혱횞혮 횞짤횞혯횞혴횞혮 횞혩횞혪횞혵횞혪횞혵 횞혬횞혷횞혯횞혵? 횞혬횞혨횞혮횞혱횞혮 횞혬횞혰횞혫횞짤?
횞짠횞혰 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혮 횞혱횞짢횞혲횞혲횞혫 횞혨횞혲횞혺, 횞짧횞짤횞혨횞혲횞짢 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혫횞혰횞혵횞혲횞혵, 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짧횞짠횞혩횞혵 횞혷횞혷횞혻횞혲 2,000 횞짤횞짠횞혵. 횞혲횞혨횞혵횞혵횞혬, 횞징횞혪횞짢횞혻횞혮 횞짖횞혻횞혲횞혲횞혺? 횞혮횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞짖횞혮횞혫 횞혷횞짢횞혪횞혲횞짤 횞짤횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혲횞짝횞혨횞짧횞혲 횞짚횞짢횞혮횞혲횞혨횞짢. 횞혲횞짝횞혨횞짧, 횞짧횞혨횞혷횞혲횞혺 횞혵횞혲. 횞징횞혪횞짢횞혻횞혮 횞짖횞혻횞혲횞혲횞혺? 횞혲횞혨횞혵횞혵횞혬, 횞혻횞짧횞짢횞혨횞혮. 횞짧횞혮횞혫횞혬 횞짢횞혩횞혬.
횞혩횞혮횞혨횞혲, 횞짠횞혮횞혻횞짠횞혮횞혺. 횞혨횞혲횞혺 횞혴횞혷횞혮 횞혱횞짢횞혲횞혲횞혫 횞혨횞혲횞혺, 횞짧횞혨횞혷횞혲횞혺 횞혵횞혲.
횞혰횞혲횞혲횞혩 횞혵횞혫횞혩횞짢 횞짖횞혶 횞혬횞혩횞혮횞징 횞짤횞혵횞혳.
횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혲횞혮횞혫횞짖, 횞혨횞혩횞혵 횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞혻횞혲... 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞혫횞혮횞짚횞짠 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혳, 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞혫횞혮횞짚횞짠 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혳. 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞혵횞혨 횞혻횞혮횞짧횞혺 횞혵횞혳 횞혵횞혨 횞혰횞혮횞짚횞짤횞혮횞짧, 횞혵횞혨 횞혩횞혲횞혱횞혮횞혰 횞짢횞짚횞혮횞혨횞혲, 횞혵횞혨 횞혴횞혵횞혮횞혶.
횞혻횞혮, 횞혨횞혩횞혵 횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혨횞짖횞짤횞혬? 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혷횞짤횞짧횞짚횞혵 횞짚횞짖횞혶 횞혨횞혰횞짢 횞짚횞짖횞혶. 횞혻횞혮, 횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혨횞짤... 횞혫횞혩횞짢 횞혨횞혲횞짧횞혮, 횞짧횞혪횞혲횞혫 횞혵횞혮, 횞혬횞혻횞혬, 횞짠횞혰 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞짚횞혵횞혨횞짚횞혮횞혺, 횞혫횞혩횞짢 횞혨횞혲횞짧횞혮.
횞혷횞혩횞짠횞짤 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혮, 횞혫횞혩횞짢 횞혨횞혲횞짧횞혮.
횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞혫횞혮횞짚횞짠 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혳.
횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짝횞혮횞혫횞짠, 횞혻횞혮. 횞혲횞혨횞혵횞혵횞혬. 횞혬횞혵횞혮.
횞징횞혵횞혲횞혰횞혬, 횞혯횞혮 횞혱횞짖횞혮횞짧.
횞혯횞혮 횞혱횞짖횞혮횞짧. 횞혷횞혬 횞징횞혵횞혲횞혰횞혬, 횞혱횞짖횞혮횞짧?
횞혻횞혮, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혵횞혨 횞혲횞혴횞혮횞혵 횞혵횞혬횞혪횞혲횞혫 횞혵횞혮 횞혨횞짧 횞혯횞혬, 횞혻횞혮. 횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혵횞혨 횞혲횞혴횞혮횞혵 횞혵횞혬횞혪횞혲횞혫?
횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혨횞혩횞혮횞혨 횞혨횞혵횞혲횞혮? 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혲횞혮횞혫횞짖 횞혷횞혬? 횞혵횞혨 횞짢횞짝횞혲횞짧횞혲 횞혵횞징횞짚횞짢 횞혵횞혳 횞혨횞짧 횞혯횞혬. 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혲횞혮횞혫횞짖 횞짤횞혨횞혷횞혲횞짢 횞혷횞짠횞혩횞혵 횞혲횞혮횞짧횞짢 횞혷횞혷횞혳?
횞혨횞혷횞혲횞짢 횞혷횞짠횞혩횞혵 횞혲횞혮횞짧횞짢 횞혷횞혷횞혳, 횞혵횞혨 횞짢횞짠 횞혨횞혷횞혲횞짢 횞혲횞혮횞혨횞혵.
횞혷횞혬 횞혲횞혮횞혨횞혵 횞혷횞짠횞혩횞혵횞짧? 횞혩횞짖횞짝횞혶 횞혷횞징횞짖횞혮횞혫횞혬 횞혬횞혷횞혻횞짠횞혬 횞혬횞혲횞혨 횞혬횞혲횞혰횞혲횞혫횞혬 횞짤횞혷횞짠횞혩횞혵횞짧 횞짚횞혰횞혮횞짧 횞혷횞혷횞혳. 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짢횞혨횞혲횞짧 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞짧횞혵횞혮횞짤횞혲 횞혬횞혷횞혯횞혴횞혮횞짢횞짧 횞짤횞혵횞혮? 횞짢횞혨횞혲횞짧횞혲 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞짧횞혵횞혮횞짤횞혲 횞혷횞징횞혮횞혫횞혮횞짧. 횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혷횞혫횞혩횞짢? 횞혩횞혨횞혷횞짧 횞짢횞혨횞혲횞짧횞혲. 횞짧횞혩횞혲횞혨횞혲 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞짚횞혵횞혨횞짚횞혮횞혺. 횞혩횞혩횞짠횞짤횞혬. 횞혵횞혷횞혬 횞혵횞혨 횞혨횞혷횞짢횞짧 횞혵횞혲 횞짠횞혮횞혫횞혶?
횞혨횞혲횞혯횞혬 횞짠횞혱횞짖, 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞혷횞짝횞혨 횞혵횞혲 횞짚횞짢횞혨횞혲횞혲횞짢.
횞혬횞혵횞혮, 횞혴횞혺, 횞짤횞혵횞혮횞혶.
횞혩횞징... 횞짧횞혩횞혲횞혨 횞혵횞혲 횞혫횞혮횞혫, 횞혩횞혩횞짠횞짤횞혬.
횞짤횞혵횞혮횞혶, 횞혫횞혮횞혫. 횞혩횞짖횞짝횞혩횞혲. 횞짧횞짤횞혷횞짖, 횞혯횞혬 횞혨횞혩횞짢횞혬횞혶. 횞짚횞짖횞혶 횞혨횞혰횞짢횞혮횞혻횞혬 횞짤횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혨횞혮횞혷횞짢 횞혨횞짧 횞혯횞혬, 횞혮횞혯횞혮 횞혪횞혶 횞짚횞짖횞혶 횞짢횞혨횞짤횞혮횞혻횞혬: 횞짧횞짤횞혷횞짖. 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혰횞혲횞혲횞혩 횞혵횞혬횞혪횞혲횞혫 횞혵횞혳 횞혨횞혰횞짧 횞혮횞혵횞짧횞혷횞혲횞혫, 횞혮횞짧횞징횞짧횞혴횞혵 횞혵횞혲 횞혩횞짖횞혲횞혻횞혲횞혲횞혶 횞짤횞혨횞혻횞혲
횞짧횞징횞짧횞혴횞혵 횞혵횞혲 횞혩횞짖횞혲횞혻횞혲횞혲횞혶 횞혴횞짤횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혨횞혮횞혷횞짢 횞혵횞혳 횞혨횞짧 횞혯횞혬.
횞혷횞혬 횞혻횞짤횞혷횞짖?
횞혷횞짖횞혻횞혲횞혲횞혻횞혲횞혶.
횞징횞짧횞혶, 횞징횞짧횞혶 횞짢횞짝횞혲횞짧횞혲 횞혵횞짤횞혨횞혮횞혵 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혳 횞혴횞혴횞혬, 횞징횞짧횞혶. 횞징횞짧횞혶, 횞혫횞혩횞짢 횞혨횞혲횞짧횞혮. 횞혫횞혩횞짢 횞혨횞혲횞짧횞혮. 횞혩횞혲횞혲, 횞혵횞혩횞혨횞혮횞짧. 횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬... 횞짧횞혮횞혫횞혬, 횞혩횞혲횞혲.
횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짢횞혮횞짝횞혬 횞짤횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혨횞혪횞혲횞혫 횞혵횞혮? 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짢횞혮횞짝횞혬 횞짤횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혨횞혫횞혩횞짢 횞혨횞혲횞짧횞혮? 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혷횞짠횞혩횞혵 횞혮횞혲횞혩횞짢횞짝횞혲횞혮횞짧. 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짢횞혮횞짝횞혬 횞짤횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혨횞혫횞혩횞짢 횞혨횞혲횞짧횞혮? 횞짧횞혫횞혩횞짢 횞혨횞혲횞짧횞혮. 횞혬횞혻횞혬, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혨횞혫횞혩횞짢 횞혨횞혲횞짧횞혮. 횞짖횞혯횞혮횞혩, 횞짖횞혯횞혮횞혩, 횞혻횞혮. 횞짖횞혯횞혮횞혩, 횞혻횞혮. 횞짧횞혺 횞혵횞혲 횞혩횞혩횞짠횞짤횞혬 횞혨횞짧 횞혫횞혮횞혫. 횞짤횞혵횞혮횞혶. 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞짚횞혬 횞혷횞혫횞혩횞짢 횞혩횞짤횞혷횞혮 횞짤횞혵 횞혨횞혵횞혲. 횞혨횞혵횞혲, 횞혴횞혺. 횞짤횞혷횞짖, 횞혯횞혬 횞혵횞혨 횞혩횞징횞혫횞짢 횞짤횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혷횞짧횞혻횞혬횞혪 횞혨횞혵횞혲횞혮. 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞혷횞짤횞짠횞혲횞짖 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞짧횞혰횞짧 횞짤횞혵횞혮 횞혩횞짖횞혩횞혮횞혫횞혬 횞혬횞혯횞혨횞짧, 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞짠횞혮횞짢횞짖 횞혨횞짧 횞짖횞짝횞혷횞혮, 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞짠횞혮횞짢횞짖 횞혨횞짧 횞혯횞혬, 횞혮횞혷횞혬 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞혷횞짠횞혩횞혵 횞혩횞혰횞혯횞짢횞혬? 횞혻횞혨횞혫횞혬 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞혷횞짠횞혩횞혵. 횞혴횞혵횞혮횞혶 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞혵횞혨 횞혷횞짠횞혩횞혵 횞혷횞혷횞혳. 횞혵횞혨 횞혩횞혲횞혱횞혮횞혰 횞짢횞짚횞혮횞혨횞혲, 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞혵횞혨 횞혷횞짠횞혩횞혵 횞혷횞혷횞혳, 횞혵횞혨 횞혰횞혮횞짚횞짤횞혮횞짧, 횞혵횞혨 횞혴횞혵횞혮횞혶.
횞혴횞혺.
횞혴횞혺, 횞혩횞혫횞혲횞혮횞짠, 횞혩횞혫횞혲횞혮횞짠, 횞혴횞혺, 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞짚횞혬 횞혵횞혲횞혫횞혲, 횞혴횞혺, 횞혬횞혻횞혬,
횞혬횞혻횞혬, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혨횞혷횞징횞혮횞짢 횞혵횞혮, 횞혴횞혺, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혨횞혷횞징횞혮횞짢 횞혵횞혮, 횞혩횞혫횞혲횞혮횞짠.
횞혻횞혮, 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혷횞짚횞혮횞혱횞짢.
횞혨횞혶 횞혨횞짧횞혶 횞혴횞혩횞짢 횞혷횞짧횞혪횞짖횞혪횞짖횞혲횞혶 횞혵횞혰횞혩횞혮횞짢횞짧 횞혬횞짠횞혮횞혷횞혲-횞혫횞혲횞징횞혱횞혮횞짢, 횞혬횞혶 횞혲횞짤횞혲횞짢횞혮 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혩횞짠횞짤횞혬.
횞혬횞혵횞혮, 횞혬횞혵횞혮, 횞혵횞혨 횞혻횞혪횞혷횞짢, 횞혵횞혨 횞혻횞혪횞혷횞짢. 횞혻횞혮, 횞혨횞혯 횞혷횞짧횞혲 횞혨횞짧횞혶 횞혪횞혮횞혷횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞짚횞혬? 횞혲횞짤 횞혵횞혲, 횞혲횞짤 횞혵횞혲 횞혰횞혵횞혱횞혮횞짢횞혬 횞혩횞짢횞짤횞짧, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞짝횞짢횞혲횞혴횞혬 횞혵횞짖횞혯횞혮횞짢.
횞혻횞혮, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혵횞혨 횞혷횞혨횞혷횞혲횞혻횞혬 횞혵횞혳 횞혨횞짧 횞혯횞혬, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혵횞혨 횞혷횞혨횞혷횞혲횞혻횞혬 횞혵횞혳 횞혨횞짧 횞혯횞혬. 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혨횞혪횞혲횞혫 횞혵횞혳 횞혷횞짧횞혲. 횞혯횞짢횞혯횞혮 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞짖횞혻횞혲횞혲횞혻횞혲횞혶.
횞혷횞혻횞혲횞혲횞짠횞혲.
횞혩횞혲횞혲, 횞혨횞혲횞혯횞혬 횞혴횞혲횞짙 횞혵횞혻횞혮 횞혩횞혲횞혰횞혫. 횞혻횞혴횞혮횞혺, 횞혻횞혴횞혮횞혺, 횞혨횞혰, 횞혮횞혮횞혨횞혲, 횞혷횞짚횞혵횞혪횞짧 횞짤횞혵횞혲. 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혪횞혶 횞혨횞혷횞혨 횞혮횞혪횞혶 횞혰횞혩횞짢 횞짤횞혵횞혲. 횞혩횞혱횞혰, 횞혻횞혴횞혮횞혺. 횞혻횞혴횞혮횞혺, 횞혵횞혲횞혻횞혮횞혯횞혨횞혮횞짢 횞짠횞혱횞혺, 횞혫횞혲, 횞혫횞혲. 횞혨횞혮횞혲, 횞혨횞혲횞혯횞혬 횞혰횞혷횞혮횞혫. 횞혬횞혻횞혬, 횞혪횞혶 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혰횞혷횞혮횞혫횞혲횞혻횞혲, 횞짧횞짢횞혨횞혮 횞혨횞혲횞혯횞혬 횞혰횞혷횞혮횞혫 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혮. 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혮 횞혰횞혷횞혮횞혫, 횞혻횞혴횞혮횞혺? 횞혨횞혮횞혲, 횞혨횞혲횞혯횞혬 횞혲횞혵횞혫 횞혰횞혷횞혮횞혫. 횞혰횞혷횞혮횞혫, 횞혲횞혮횞짚횞혲.
횞혴횞혺 횞혰횞혷횞혮횞혫횞혲. 횞혻횞혬횞혻횞혲횞혶? 횞혴횞혺. 횞혲횞혮횞짚횞혲. 횞혨횞혩횞혨, 횞혨횞혲횞혳 횞혩횞혨횞짧횞혲 횞혵횞짖횞혮횞혵횞혶?
횞혨횞혬, 횞혴횞혺 횞혰횞혷횞혮횞혫. 횞짖횞혫횞혴횞혻횞짧 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혲, 횞혨횞혬?
횞혵횞혲횞혻횞혮횞혯횞혨횞혮횞짢 횞짠횞혱횞혺, 횞짧횞짢횞혨횞혬, 횞혰횞혷횞혮횞혫, 횞짧횞짢횞혨횞혬.
횞혷횞혬 횞짠횞혮횞짢횞혬? 횞혨횞혲횞혳 횞혩횞혨횞짧 횞혵횞짖횞혮횞혵횞혶? 횞짧횞짢횞혨횞혬, 횞혴횞혵 횞혬횞징횞혲횞짚횞혮횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞짤횞혷횞징횞짚횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞혵횞혳 횞혩횞혪횞혺 횞짖횞혵 횞혬횞짝횞혲횞짚횞혮횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞혮횞혬횞혫횞혩횞혮횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞혮횞혬횞짚횞짢횞짚횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞혮횞혯횞혬 횞짤횞혲횞짤 횞혵횞혳 횞징횞혲횞혫횞혬 횞혮횞짤횞혬횞혲횞혵횞혫 횞혪횞혫횞혵 횞혩횞짧횞혮횞혳 횞혴횞짢횞혮횞혩, 횞혬횞혴횞혵 횞짤횞혱횞혮횞혲횞혮횞짧. 횞혯횞혬 횞짤횞혱횞혮횞혲횞혮횞짧 횞혩횞혷횞혲횞짜 횞짖횞혪횞혩횞혻횞혲횞혮횞짧. 횞혩횞혮횞혨 횞짧횞짤횞혷횞짖 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혨횞혷횞짧, 횞혰횞혷횞혮횞혫. 횞짧횞짢횞혨횞혬, 횞혷횞혬 횞짤횞짠횞혮횞짢횞혬 횞혯횞혬 횞혴횞혴횞혬.
횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혮횞혨횞혲횞혷횞혨, 횞혨횞혲횞혷횞혨 횞혮횞혨횞혩횞혨, 횞혻횞혴횞혮횞혺? 횞짖횞혴횞짤횞혲횞혮, 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮 횞혻횞짤횞혮횞혨횞혲횞혶 횞혯횞혷횞혺 횞짠횞짝횞짢, 횞혻횞혴횞혮횞혺?
횞혮횞혴횞혲횞짙 횞혵횞혻횞혮 횞혩횞혲횞혰횞혫, 횞혮횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮 횞혲횞혮횞짤횞혩횞혲횞혶 횞혩횞징횞혵횞혮횞혺 횞혮횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮 횞짢횞혮횞혨횞혲횞혶 횞혱횞혵횞혮횞혮횞혲횞혯횞혲횞혬,
횞짧횞혮횞혳 횞혴횞혫횞혲 횞혨횞혷횞혨 횞혷횞혻횞혷횞혲횞혴횞혬 횞혱횞혲횞짚횞혬 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혨횞혮횞짢횞혮횞짧 횞혩횞혩횞혲횞짧 횞혮횞혨횞혯 횞혻횞혬횞혲횞혬 횞혴횞혯횞혬 횞혷횞짖횞혮횞혷횞짖횞혶 횞혬횞혴횞혵 횞혮횞혬횞혲횞혨 횞혨횞혮횞혷횞짢횞짧 횞혵횞혲: 횞혨횞혮횞혵횞혲 횞짧횞짤횞혲횞혶 횞혷횞혮횞혯횞혲횞짠횞혬 횞혮횞혨횞혯 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혲횞짤횞짢 횞혲횞혫횞짖횞짧횞혲 횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞혷횞혨 횞혨횞혮횞혬횞혩횞짧, 횞짤횞혷횞짧횞혲 횞혵횞혬 횞혷횞혮횞혯횞혲횞짠횞혬 횞혴횞혯횞혬 횞혵횞징횞혵횞혮횞혨횞혮, 횞짠횞짝횞짧 횞혷횞혲횞혵 횞징횞혫횞짠횞혬,
횞짚횞혮횞혵 횞짖횞혻횞짠횞혬,
횞짝횞혩횞혲횞짠횞혬 횞짚횞혲, 횞혴횞혵 횞혷횞혲횞혻횞혲 횞혴횞혨횞혵횞혬 횞혮횞혨횞혯 횞짤횞혷횞혻횞혮 횞혵횞혻횞혮 횞혴횞혯횞혬 횞혷횞혮횞혯횞혲횞짠횞혬 횞혩횞혴횞혲횞짙. 횞혮횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞혰횞짢횞혲 횞짤횞짤횞혷횞짖횞짧횞혶? 횞혷횞혮횞혯횞혲횞짠횞혬. 횞혴횞혺, 횞혨횞혯 횞혵횞혨 횞짢횞짠 횞혯횞혬, 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짤횞혮횞혷횞짖 횞혷횞혮횞혯횞혲횞짠횞혬, 횞혨횞혩횞혵 횞혨횞혷횞혨 횞혨횞혮횞혬횞혩횞짧 횞혲횞혲횞혺,
횞혮횞혨횞혯 횞혵횞혯횞혪횞혻횞혮 횞혵횞혻횞혮 횞혴횞혮횞징 횞혲횞혲횞혺 횞혨횞혫횞혮횞혶, 횞혮횞짖횞혮횞혫 횞혴횞혮횞징 횞혲횞혲횞혺 횞혨횞혫횞혮횞혶, 횞혮횞혨횞혯 횞혬횞짚횞징횞짠횞혻횞혮 횞혵횞징횞짚횞혮횞짢 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혲횞혲횞혺 횞혨횞혫횞혮횞혶. 횞혮횞혨횞혰횞짢횞혲 횞혯횞혬 횞짤횞짧횞혲횞짧횞혶. 횞혮횞혬횞짧횞혰횞혵횞혻횞혮 횞혵횞짢횞짠횞혮횞혫, 횞혬횞짧횞혰횞혵횞혻횞혮 횞혵횞짢횞짠횞혮횞혫 횞짝횞혷횞혮횞혫,
횞짝횞혷횞혮횞혫, 횞짝횞혷횞혮횞혫, 횞혮횞짢횞짠횞혫횞혻횞혮 횞혮횞혬횞혲횞짧횞혬 횞혬횞혨횞혮횞혮횞혲횞짢횞혬 횞혬횞혻횞혮횞짢횞혨 횞혻횞혮횞짢횞혨 횞혰횞혷횞혬. 횞혮횞혨횞혯, 횞혮횞혨횞혯 횞짚횞짧횞혨횞혮횞혶 횞혫횞짚횞혲횞짠횞혮횞짧 횞혩횞혫횞혵횞짧, 횞혫횞짚횞혲횞짠횞혮횞짧 횞혩횞혫횞혵횞짧, 횞혮횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮 횞혨횞혮횞혷횞짢횞혲횞혶, 횞혷횞혲 횞혯횞혬 횞혲횞혴횞혮횞혵 횞혵횞혬횞혲횞혮횞짧 횞혩횞짤횞짖횞혬 횞혬횞혯횞혨횞짧? 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮 횞혷횞혷횞짤 횞혵횞혨 횞혲횞혫횞짖횞혻횞혮 횞혷횞혬 횞짠횞혮횞짢횞혬.
횞짚횞짧횞혰횞혻횞혮 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혫횞혵횞짧, 횞혮횞혷횞혲 횞짖횞혷횞혫 횞혷횞혮횞혵횞혻횞혮?
횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혬횞혰횞혷횞혮횞혫, 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짖횞혷횞혫횞짧 횞혩횞혫횞혵횞짧. 횞혬횞혻횞혬, 횞혬횞혪횞짖횞짧 횞혵횞짖횞혮횞혵횞혶,
횞혻횞혬횞짢횞징 횞혵횞혻횞혮 횞혬횞짢횞혲횞짠횞혮횞혯 횞짤횞혵횞혮, 횞혨횞혩횞혵 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혬횞혲횞혲횞짧, 횞혨횞혲횞혯횞혬 횞혴횞혲횞짙 횞혬횞혲횞혬, 횞혮횞혷횞혨횞혯 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮 횞혩횞혲횞혰횞혫, 횞혩횞혺 횞짠횞혱횞혺 횞혮횞혰횞혷횞혮횞혫 횞짤횞혵횞혲, 횞혨횞혬? 횞혴횞혺. 횞혩횞혲횞혰횞혫, 횞혴횞혴횞혬 횞혩횞혨횞짧 횞혵횞짖횞혮횞혵횞혶, 횞혬횞혩횞혻횞짧? 횞혴횞혺. 횞혲횞혮횞짚횞혲.
횞혮횞혲횞짤 횞혵횞혲 횞짖횞혮횞혫 횞짤횞혨횞혵횞혬.
횞짖횞혵 횞혷횞혻횞짧 횞짤횞혬횞혨횞혲횞짤횞혬 횞짧횞혰횞혮횞혮횞혬 횞혨횞혮횞짢횞혪횞혯횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞혲횞혱횞혲횞짧, 횞혨횞혯 횞짝횞짢횞혲횞혳 횞혵횞혰횞혫횞혮횞짢 횞혵횞혻횞짠횞혮횞혫횞짧 횞짤횞혪'횞혲 횞혵횞짚횞혻횞혲 횞혬횞짧횞혴횞혮횞혮횞짝횞혮횞짧 횞혬횞혮횞혮횞혪횞혲횞혻횞혬, 횞혨횞혮 횞혨횞혰횞짢횞혲 횞혬횞혵횞혲횞혩횞혲횞혫횞혮 횞혬횞혷횞짠횞징횞혲횞혷횞혵횞혲?
횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혵횞혨 횞혲횞혮횞혫횞짖.
횞짖횞짢횞혩 횞혱횞혮횞혩, 횞혨횞짢횞혲, 횞짧횞짠횞짝횞혲횞짢 횞혬횞혰횞혫횞짤횞혮횞짧, 횞혴횞혨횞혺 횞혩횞혷횞혩횞혯횞짠 횞짤횞혵 횞혯'횞혨횞짠 횞혩횞짖횞짢횞혮횞짜 횞혬횞짠횞혬횞혲횞혵횞짧횞혲 횞짤횞혵횞혴횞혶.
횞혬횞혯횞혷횞짢 횞혬횞혨횞혷횞짢횞혲횞짠횞혻횞혲, 횞혷횞혲횞혲횞짠횞혵 횞혪'횞짠횞징횞혮횞혺,
횞짤횞혮횞혩 횞혲횞혱횞짢횞혲횞혫 횞혲횞혵횞혫, 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞짖횞혩횞짢 횞혻횞혲횞짧횞혮횞혰 횞짚횞혵횞징횞혱횞혲, 횞혮횞혴횞짖횞짧 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞혷횞짧횞혰횞혩횞혨 횞혩횞징횞혮횞짚횞짢횞혷횞짢횞짠횞혱.
횞짢횞짠 횞혩횞혺 횞혨횞혫횞혶 횞혨횞혰횞혫 횞혲횞혴횞혮횞혵 횞혵횞혷횞짝횞혮횞혨 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혮.
횞혨횞짤횞짢 횞혷횞짚횞혮횞짢횞징횞혶 횞혲횞혬횞혮횞혲횞짠횞혲횞혺 횞혩횞짢횞짠횞혮횞혫.
횞혻횞혴횞혻횞징횞짧횞혲 횞혵횞징횞혮횞짚횞짢 횞짖횞혵 횞혷횞혻횞짧 횞혵횞혵횞혴횞혮횞혫 횞혨횞짧 횞혷횞혲횞혲횞짠횞혵 횞혪'횞짠횞징횞혮횞혺.
횞혨횞혮횞혵횞혲 횞혯횞혬 횞혯횞혬?
횞혬횞혲횞혲, 횞혩횞짖횞짝횞혶 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞혲횞혴횞혮횞혵 횞혵횞혬횞혲횞혮횞짧 횞혴횞혵 횞혫횞혩횞짢.
횞혵횞짚횞짧횞짖, 횞혬횞혩횞짢횞혲횞짠 횞짢횞짖횞혲횞혮횞혺 횞혩횞혷횞혮횞혰횞혲, 횞짤횞혬횞짚횞혳 횞혵횞혰횞징횞혬,
횞혮횞혴횞혳 횞혬횞혪횞혲횞짖횞혬 횞혵횞징횞혲횞혮횞혷횞혬 횞혬횞혷횞혮횞짝횞혵횞혰 횞짧횞짖횞혵횞혮횞혷횞혬 횞혬횞혷횞징횞짧횞혮횞짢횞혲횞짧.
횞짧횞혪횞혲횞혫 횞혵횞혲, 횞혨횞혫횞혮횞혻횞혲,
횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혲횞혮횞혫횞짖 횞혨횞혲횞혳 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혲횞혮횞짝횞혨 횞혷횞혴횞혨횞혺 횞혵횞혴횞혲횞혮횞혮횞혺 횞짧횞혵 횞혨횞혩횞혲횞혩? 횞짧횞혵 횞혨횞혩횞혲횞혩? 횞혴횞혺. 횞혩횞혮횞혨 횞혨횞혰횞짢횞혲횞혲, 횞짧횞짢횞혨횞혬.
횞짤횞혩횞혮횞짢, 횞짤횞혩횞혮횞짢 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혬횞혪횞혬.
횞짤횞혩횞혮횞짢, 횞짤횞혩횞혮횞짢. 횞짝횞혨횞짧, 횞짠횞혫횞혶 횞짠횞짝횞짧, 횞짠횞혫횞혶. 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짢횞혮횞혨횞혬 횞짤횞혶?
횞징횞짖 횞혨횞혰횞짢횞혲횞혲, 횞징횞짖.
횞징횞짖, 횞혲횞짤 횞혵횞혳 횞짖횞혮횞혫.
횞징횞짖, 횞징횞짖. 횞혩횞혮횞혨, 횞혲횞짤 횞혵횞혳 횞짖횞혮횞혫. 횞징횞짖!
횞징횞짖, 횞징횞짖, 횞혲횞짤 횞혵횞혳 횞짖횞혮횞혫. 횞징횞짖!
횞징횞짖, 횞징횞짖, 횞징횞짖, 횞징횞짖! 횞짖횞짢횞혩 횞혱횞혮횞혩 횞혵횞혴횞혶 횞짤횞혬횞혮횞혩횞혨 횞혵횞혻횞혮 횞혩횞짧횞혮횞혴횞혻횞혲횞짧횞혻횞혮 "횞혬횞혴횞짢횞혮횞혻횞혲횞짠횞혬 횞혬횞혻횞혲횞혲횞혫횞짧",
횞혮횞혬횞짚횞짖횞혶 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮 횞혻횞혨횞짢횞혰 횞혩횞짧횞혮횞혴횞혻횞혲횞짧횞혻횞혮 횞혷횞짤횞혮횞짢횞짢 횞짝횞혩횞혨횞혲.
횞짤횞혵횞혮횞혶 횞혵횞혳, 횞혷횞짢, 횞혰횞혲횞혲횞혶 횞짠횞혮횞짢횞혻횞징. 횞짖횞짢횞혩 횞혱횞혮횞혩. 횞혮횞혩횞혴횞혺, 횞혰횞혲횞혲횞혶 횞짠횞혮횞짢횞혻횞징 횞혮횞혷횞짤횞혮횞짢횞짢 횞짝횞혩횞혨횞혲, 횞혷횞혬 횞혯횞혬 횞혨횞혮횞혷횞짢, 횞혰횞혲횞혲횞혶, 횞혮횞혨횞혲횞혯횞혬 횞혫횞혩횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혴횞혮횞짧횞혩?
횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혷횞짤횞혮횞짢횞짢 횞짝횞혩횞혨횞혲, 횞혯횞혬 횞짧횞짠횞혺 횞혩횞짝횞혩횞혨.
횞혨횞혻횞혲, 횞혵횞혫횞혮횞혪횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞혰횞짢횞혨횞혲 횞혵횞혷횞짤횞짚횞혱횞혲횞혶 횞혴횞혷횞혮 "횞혰횞혲횞혲횞혵 횞혬횞혷횞혰횞혻횞혬 횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞혩횞혲횞짧횞혳, 횞혨횞짤횞혷횞혮횞짢 횞짖횞혵 횞혻횞혲횞짠횞혲횞혮횞혻횞혮".
횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혨횞혰횞짢횞혨횞혲, 횞혵횞혫횞혮횞혪횞혷횞혬, "횞혰횞혲횞혲횞혵 횞짤횞짚횞짢 횞혬횞혮횞짚횞짖횞짧횞혳".
횞혮횞짖횞혮횞혫 횞혴횞혬횞혻횞혬 횞혮횞혴횞혬횞혻횞혬 횞혫횞혮횞혪횞혷횞혨횞혮횞짧. 횞혲횞혮횞짧횞짢 횞혫횞혯횞짖횞혬 횞혩횞혨횞혲횞혷횞혮횞혻횞혲횞혶. 횞짚횞혰횞혮횞짧 횞혫횞혶 횞혩횞짠횞짢횞혩, 횞혯횞혬 횞짤횞혵횞혲. 횞혮횞혩횞혴횞혺, 횞혨횞혲횞혺 횞징횞짚횞짠 횞짤횞혰횞혵횞짠 횞혪횞혫횞혮횞혵 횞혷횞짤횞혲횞짢횞혲횞혳 횞짤횞혪횞혮횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞짖횞혵 횞짚횞혲 횞혴횞혮횞혵횞혶.
횞혷횞혬 횞혴횞짧횞혩횞짧 횞혩횞짖횞혩횞짢?
횞혩횞짖횞혩횞짢 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혬횞혲횞혲횞짧횞혲 횞혷횞짤횞혮횞짢횞짢 횞짤횞혲횞짢횞혮횞짧횞혲횞혶.
횞혷횞혬 횞혯횞혬 횞혨횞혮횞혷횞짢?
횞혷횞혬 횞혯횞혬 횞혨횞혮횞혷횞짢? 횞혵횞혫횞혮횞혪횞혷횞혬, 횞짢횞혮횞짧횞혲 횞혻횞혮횞짧횞혻횞짧, 횞혯횞혬 횞짤횞혵횞혲.
횞혨횞혯횞짢횞혰 횞혲횞짠횞짢, 횞혨횞혯횞짢횞혰 횞혰횞혩횞혲횞혩, 횞혨횞짤횞짧횞혺 횞혲횞짤횞짢 횞혮횞혵횞혨 횞징횞혩횞혲횞혩, 횞혯횞혬 횞짤횞혵횞혲.
횞혨횞혻횞혲, 횞혵횞혫횞혮횞혪횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞혰횞혫 횞혷횞혨횞혵횞혬 횞짤횞혬횞혷횞짝횞혲횞혨횞혮, 횞혯횞혮 횞혬횞혲횞혲횞짧횞혬 횞짠횞혮횞혻횞징횞짚횞짝횞혲횞혬 횞혷횞혲횞혮횞혰횞혫횞짧 횞짤횞혵횞혲 횞혮횞짤횞혵 횞혰횞혩횞짢 횞혱횞혮횞혩 횞짤횞혵횞혲.
횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮 횞혩횞혲횞혰횞혫, 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮 횞혬횞혷횞짝횞혨횞혻횞혮 횞혨횞짧 횞짚횞혲횞혻횞혪 횞짚횞혮횞혻횞혪 횞짤횞혲횞짢횞혮횞짧횞혲횞혶.
횞짠횞혫횞혲횞혷횞혬 횞혴횞짧횞혮횞혩 횞혵횞혳,
횞징횞짧횞혴횞혵 횞혲횞혷횞혲횞혻횞혬,
횞혴횞짧횞혮횞혩 횞혵횞혳, 횞징횞짧횞혴횞혵 횞짤횞혷횞혨횞혵횞혬, 횞혴횞짧횞혮횞혩 횞혵횞혳, 횞징횞짧횞혴횞혵 횞혲횞혷횞혲횞혻횞혬 횞혮횞혨횞혯 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혴횞혵 횞혬횞혯횞혷횞혺 횞혴횞혴횞혬, 횞혯횞혬 횞짤횞혵횞혲. 횞혨횞혷횞혮횞짢 횞혵횞혲, 횞혨횞혰횞혫 횞혬횞혫횞혩횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞짤횞혻횞혮횞짢횞혨 횞징횞짠횞짢횞혻횞혮 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혲 횞혩횞혻횞혮횞짤횞혨 횞혬횞혯횞혬,
횞혬횞혨횞혶 횞혷횞징횞짚횞짢횞혲 횞혬횞혱횞혵횞짚횞혮횞혺 횞짤횞혵 횞혬횞혩횞혰횞혮횞짢횞혮횞짧 횞혬횞혨횞혫횞혷횞혮횞혻횞혲횞혮횞짧 횞짤횞혵횞짚횞짖횞혷횞혲횞혶 횞혷횞짝횞혮횞혲횞짢횞혮횞짧 횞혷횞혷횞짤 횞짖횞혵 횞혬횞혫횞혵횞짧,
횞혬횞혨횞혶 횞혨횞혵횞혮 횞혬횞혶 횞혷횞징횞짚횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞혨횞혷횞혲횞짧횞혲횞혲횞혶? 횞짚횞혲횞짠횞혱횞혲횞혩횞혲횞혲횞혶, 횞짚횞혲횞짠횞혱횞혲횞혩횞혲횞혲횞혶 횞혯횞혮횞혬횞혲 횞짚횞짢횞혮횞혯횞혬,
횞혨횞혷횞혻횞혮횞짧횞혲, 횞혨횞혷횞혻횞혮횞짧횞혲, 횞혴횞혵 횞혨횞혷횞혻횞혮횞짧횞혲. 횞혮횞혩횞혴횞혺, 횞혵횞혨횞혰횞짢 횞짠횞짢횞혲횞혲횞짢횞혬 횞짖횞짤횞혲횞짢횞혬 횞짤횞혴횞혯횞혮, 횞혷횞혬 횞짖횞혮횞혫 횞혻횞혮횞짧횞짢 횞혵횞혳 횞혵횞짖횞짧횞혲횞혫?
횞혵횞짖횞짧횞혲횞혫 횞혻횞혮횞짧횞짢 횞혵횞혲 횞짢횞짠 횞혵횞혴횞짧횞혮횞혩 횞혵횞짠횞혮횞혷횞혫횞혲횞징 횞혱횞혮횞혩.
횞혲횞짚횞혬? 횞혮횞혩횞혴횞혺, 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮 횞혷횞혨횞혰횞혵횞혲횞혶 횞혵횞혳 횞혩횞혬횞짝횞혵횞혰횞혬. 횞짧횞혮횞혫횞혬 횞짢횞혩횞혬. 횞짧횞혮횞혫횞혬 횞짤횞혬횞혲횞혲횞짧횞혶 횞혨횞혲횞짧횞혻횞혮. 횞혵횞혬횞짧횞짢횞혨횞혮횞짧 횞혩횞짤횞혩횞혮횞짖 횞혬횞혩횞혨. 횞혵횞혬횞짧횞짢횞혨횞혮횞짧.
횞징횞짖, 횞징횞짖, 횞혰횞혩횞혵! 횞혷횞혬? 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혲횞혴횞혮횞혵 횞혵횞혫횞혩횞짢 횞혨횞혲횞짧횞혳? 횞짚횞혬. 횞짧횞짢횞혨횞혬, 횞혨횞짧횞혷횞혮횞혵 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혬횞혲횞혲횞짧횞혲 횞혩횞짚횞혨횞혩.
횞혵횞혨, 횞혵횞혨, 횞혨횞짧횞혷횞혮횞혵 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혬횞혲횞혲횞짧횞혲 횞혩... 횞혩횞혷횞징횞혲횞혩횞혬 횞짤횞혵 횞짢횞혮횞짧횞혲. 횞혬횞혲횞혲, 횞혮횞혵횞혨 횞혨횞혷횞짢횞짧 횞혵횞혲? 횞혵횞혨, 횞혵횞혨, 횞혵횞혨, 횞혷횞혬 횞짚횞짧횞혨횞혮횞혶. 횞혨횞짧횞혷횞혮횞혵 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혬횞혲횞혲횞짧횞혲 횞혩... 횞혩횞혫횞혲횞징횞짠횞혮횞혱횞짠 횞혬횞혰횞혫횞짤 횞짤횞짚횞짧횞혰횞혮 횞혩횞짚횞혲횞혻횞혬? 횞혵횞혨, 횞혵횞혨, 횞혵횞혨, 횞혨횞짧횞혷횞혮횞혵 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혬횞혲횞혲횞짧횞혲 횞혩횞혩횞혻횞짠.
횞혨횞혬. 횞혩횞혩횞혻횞짠. 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혬횞혲횞혲횞짧횞혲 횞혩횞혩횞혻횞짠, 횞짖횞혷횞혫횞짧횞혲 횞혩횞짧횞혮횞짢 횞혮횞혰횞짤횞혩횞짧횞혲 횞짖횞혵 횞혬... 횞짖횞혵 횞혬횞혨횞혮횞혩횞짢횞혫횞짢횞짚횞혱.
횞혵횞혨, 횞혵횞혨, 횞짖횞혷횞혫횞짧횞혲 횞혮횞혰횞짤횞혩횞짧횞혲 횞짖횞혵 횞혬... 횞짖횞혵 횞혬횞짚횞짠횞혲횞혫횞혬 횞혬횞혯횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혰횞혫횞짤횞혬 횞혬횞혰횞짧횞혲횞혴횞혬 횞짤횞혶. 횞혵횞혨, 횞혵횞혨, 횞혷횞혬 횞짚횞짧횞혨횞혮횞혶? 횞짖횞혷횞혫횞짧횞혲 횞혮횞혰횞짤횞혩횞짧횞혲 횞짖횞혵 횞혬... 횞혬횞혲, 횞짖횞혵 횞혬횞혴횞징횞짙 횞짤횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혰횞혲횞혲횞혩횞혳 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혨횞혰횞혯횞혲횞짢 횞혵횞혳. 횞혵횞혨, 횞짖횞혷횞혫횞짧횞혲 횞혮횞혰횞짤횞혩횞짧횞혲 횞짖횞혵 횞혬횞혷횞짖횞짢횞혴횞짧 횞혲횞혰횞징횞혲횞혶 횞혩횞혲횞혻횞혲횞혻횞혮.
횞혨횞혬.
횞짧횞짢횞혨횞혬, 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혮횞혨횞혻횞혲, 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮... 횞혬횞짢횞혲 횞짧횞혴횞혻횞혻횞혮 횞혨횞짧횞혷횞혮횞혵 횞혵횞짠횞혻횞혮횞짧 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혱횞혵횞혮횞혮횞혲횞혯횞혲횞혬. 횞혵횞혨, 횞혵횞혨, 횞혵횞혨, 횞혷횞혬 횞짚횞짧횞혨횞혮횞혶, 횞혷횞혬 횞짚횞짧횞혨횞혮횞혶? 횞짖횞혷횞혫횞혻횞혮... 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혮횞혨횞혻횞혲, 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮, 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮... 횞혨횞짧횞혷횞혮횞혵 횞혷횞혴횞짢횞혻횞혮 횞혵횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혨횞혮횞혱횞혮 횞혮횞혵횞혨 횞짤횞혲횞혵횞혷횞혻횞혮 횞혨횞짧... 횞혵횞혨, 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮... 횞혨횞혯 횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮 횞짤횞혮횞짧횞짚횞혲횞혶 횞혩횞혨횞혮횞짚횞혺... 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮 횞혷횞혴횞혲횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞혨횞혰횞혫 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞짤횞혻횞혲 횞혴횞혩횞짢 횞혬횞짢횞혩횞혬 횞짤횞혻횞혲횞혶,
횞짧횞짢횞혨횞혬, 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혮횞혨횞혻횞혲, 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮... 횞혬횞짢횞혲 횞짧횞혴횞혻횞혻횞혮 횞혨횞짧횞혷횞혮횞혵 횞혵횞짠횞혻횞혮횞짧 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혱횞혵횞혮횞혮횞혲횞혯횞혲횞혬. 횞혵횞혨, 횞혵횞혨, 횞혵횞혨, 횞혷횞혬 횞짚횞짧횞혨횞혮횞혶, 횞혷횞혬 횞짚횞짧횞혨횞혮횞혶? 횞짖횞혷횞혫횞혻횞혮...
횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혮횞혨횞혻횞혲, 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮, 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮... 횞혨횞짧횞혷횞혮횞혵 횞혷횞혴횞짢횞혻횞혮 횞혵횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혨횞혮횞혱횞혮 횞혮횞혵횞혨 횞짤횞혲횞혵횞혷횞혻횞혮 횞혨횞짧... 횞혵횞혨, 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮... 횞혨횞혯 횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮 횞짤횞혮횞짧횞짚횞혲횞혶 횞혩횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혮... 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮 횞혷횞혴횞혲횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞혨횞혰횞혫 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞짤횞혻횞혲 횞혴횞혩횞짢 횞혬횞짢횞혩횞혬 횞짤횞혻횞혲횞혶, 횞혻횞혴횞혮횞혺? 횞혷횞혨횞혯 횞혬횞짝횞혩횞혨, 횞혻횞혴횞혮횞혺? 횞혻횞혴횞혮횞혺. 횞혮횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞짢횞혮횞짝횞혬 횞혵횞혫횞짖횞짧, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞짢횞혮횞짝횞혬 횞혵횞혫횞짖횞짧, 횞혵횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짧횞혷횞혲횞혫... 횞혷횞혬, 횞혵횞혨 횞짠횞혮횞혻횞혬 횞혵횞혳 횞혷횞짧횞혻횞혬 횞혵횞혲횞혮횞혶 횞혬횞혮횞혵횞혫횞짧? 횞징횞혵횞혲횞혰횞혬, 횞혨횞혶 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞짤횞혴횞혰횞짧횞혲. 횞혵횞혨, 횞혵횞혨, 횞혵횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짧횞혷횞혲횞혫... 횞혵횞혨 횞혷횞혰횞혯횞혲횞짢 횞혵횞혳 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혴횞징횞짙? 횞짖횞혮횞혫 횞짚횞짖횞혶 횞혷횞짧횞혲 횞짖횞혶 횞혬횞혴횞징횞짙
횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혮횞혨횞혻횞혲, 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮, 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮... 횞혨횞짧횞혷횞혮횞혵 횞혷횞혴횞짢횞혻횞혮 횞혵횞혬횞혮횞혨 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혨횞혮횞혱횞혮 횞혮횞혵횞혨 횞짢횞짠 횞짤횞혲횞혵횞혷횞혻횞혮 횞혨횞짧... 횞혵횞혨, 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮... 횞혨횞혯 횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮 횞짤횞혮횞짧횞짚횞혲횞혶 횞혩횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혮... 횞혨횞혻횞혰횞혻횞혮 횞혷횞혴횞혲횞짢횞혲횞혶 횞혨횞혰횞혫 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞짤횞혵횞혲 횞혴횞혩횞짢 횞혬횞짢횞혩횞혬 횞짤횞혻횞혲횞혶, 횞혻횞혴횞혮횞혺? 횞혷횞혨횞혯 횞혬횞짝횞혩횞혨, 횞혻횞혴횞혮횞혺? 횞혻횞혴횞혮횞혺. 횞혮횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞짢횞혮횞짝횞혬 횞혵횞혫횞짖횞짧, 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞짢횞혮횞짝횞혬 횞혵횞혫횞짖횞짧, 횞혵횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짧횞혷횞혲횞혫... 횞혷횞혬, 횞혵횞혨 횞짠횞혮횞혻횞혬 횞혵횞혳 횞혷횞짧횞혻횞혬 횞혵횞혲횞혮횞혶 횞혬횞혮횞혵횞혫횞짧? 횞징횞혵횞혲횞혰횞혬, 횞혬횞혨횞혶 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞짤횞혴횞혰횞짧? 횞혵횞혨, 횞혵횞혨, 횞혵횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짧횞혷횞혲횞혫... 횞혵횞혨, 횞혷횞혰횞혯횞혲횞짢 횞혵횞혳 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혴횞징횞짙? 횞짖횞혮횞혫 횞짚횞짖횞혶 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짖횞혶 횞혬횞혴횞징횞짙? 횞혵횞혨, 횞혵횞혨, 횞혵횞혨, 횞혵횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짧횞혷횞혲횞혫... 횞혵횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞짧횞혷횞혲횞혫 횞혷횞징횞짧횞혴횞혵 횞짖횞혵 횞혬횞혰횞혫횞짢횞혬 횞짤횞혵횞혳 횞혴횞혴횞혬 횞혩횞혨횞혲횞혯횞혬 횞혷횞혲횞혺... 횞혵횞혨, 횞혷횞혬 횞짚횞짧횞혨횞혮횞혶? 횞혵횞혷횞혬 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞짧횞혷
횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혵횞혨 횞혷횞혩횞혲횞혺 횞혨횞짧 횞혯횞혬!
횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞짧횞혬 횞혰횞혮횞짤횞혩 횞짤횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혵횞혨 횞혷횞징횞혮횞혪횞혵 횞혵...
횞혵횞혬횞짤횞혵횞혲횞혶 횞혨횞짧 횞혬횞혷횞짤횞짚횞혱횞혲횞혶 횞짤횞혵횞혲 횞혩횞짖횞짝횞혷횞혲? 횞혴횞혺! 횞혱횞혮횞혩, 횞징횞혵횞혲횞혰횞혬. 횞혨횞혬... 횞혷횞혵횞짝횞혬.
횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞짧횞혶 횞혷횞혩횞혲횞혻횞혲횞혶? 횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞짧횞혶 횞혷횞혩횞혲횞혻횞혲횞혶? 횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞짧횞혶 횞혷횞혩횞혲횞혻횞혲횞혶? 횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞짧횞혶 횞혷횞혩횞혲횞혻횞혲횞혶? 횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞짧횞혶 횞혷횞혩횞혲횞혻횞혲횞혶? 횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞짧횞혶 횞혷횞혩횞혲횞혻횞혲횞혶? 횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞짧횞혶 횞혷횞혩횞혲횞혻횞혲횞혶? 횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞짧횞혶 횞혷횞혩횞혲횞혻횞혲횞혶? 횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞짧횞혶 횞혷횞혩횞혲횞혻횞혲횞혶? 횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞짧횞혶 횞혷횞혩횞혲횞혻횞혲횞혶? 횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞짧횞혶 횞혷횞혩횞혲횞혻횞혲횞혶? 횞혷횞혬, 횞혨횞짧횞혶 횞혷횞혩횞혲횞혻횞혲횞혶? 횞혨횞혻횞혲 20 횞혮-22. 횞혨횞혬, 횞혴횞혺.
횞짧횞혮횞혫횞혬.
횞혨횞혻횞혲 횞혵횞혨 횞혷횞혩횞혲횞혺, 횞혨횞짧횞혶 20 횞혮횞혨횞짧횞혶 22?
횞혨횞혮 횞짤횞혨횞짧횞혶 20 횞혮횞혨횞짧횞혶 22?
횞혯횞혬 횞혵횞혨 횞혨횞혰횞짢횞짧. 횞혨횞혻횞혲 20 횞혮횞혨횞혻횞혲 22. 횞혯횞혬 횞혨횞혰횞짢횞짧. 횞혲횞짤 22 횞혮횞혲횞짤 22. 횞혯횞혮 횞혨횞혰횞짢횞짧, 횞혬횞혲횞혨 횞혨횞혰횞짢횞짧 횞혷횞혨횞혮횞혫 횞혰횞짤횞혮횞혩횞혬.
횞혬횞혲횞혨 20 횞혮횞혨횞혻횞혲 22. 횞혵횞혨, 횞혵횞혨.
횞짧횞짠횞짤횞혲횞혩 횞혵횞혲 횞혩횞짠횞짢횞혲횞혨횞혮횞짧. 횞혲횞짤 22,
Yes, put it on the side. There is one thing and there is 22. 22 and 22. There is two, two, two different things.
- 횞혨횞혩횞혵 there is no gift.
- there is no gift.
- but there is nothing different.
- there is one 22 and one 22, two.
- one 23 and one 22.
- 횞혯횞혬 횞혵횞혨 횞혬횞혴횞혵횞혵.
- 횞혬횞혵횞혮, 횞혬횞혵횞혮, 횞혬횞혵횞혮.
- 횞혬횞혵횞혮, 횞혬횞혵횞혮, 횞혬횞혵횞혮, 횞혩횞혲횞혫횞징.
- how old are you?
- 횞혬횞혵횞혮, 횞혷횞혬 횞짠횞짢횞혬?
- 횞혷횞혬 횞짠횞짢횞혬?
- 횞혨횞혲횞짚횞혬 횞혬횞혲횞혨?
- 횞혨횞혲횞짚횞혬 횞혯횞혨횞짧 횞짤횞혨횞혮횞혷횞짢횞짧 횞혬횞짠횞혮횞혷횞혫횞혲횞징횞혱횞혮횞짢 횞혻횞혪횞혷횞짢?
- 횞혷횞혬 횞짠횞혮횞짢횞혬?
- 횞짤횞짝횞짢횞혲횞혳 횞혨횞혮횞짧횞혬 횞혬횞혲횞혨 횞혻횞혮횞짚횞혵.
- 횞짤횞혵횞혨 횞짝횞짢횞혲횞혳 횞혬횞혲횞혨 횞혩횞짖횞혲횞혬 횞혴횞혵 횞혬횞혯횞혷횞혺.
- 횞혷횞혬 횞짠횞혮횞짢횞혬?
- 횞혬횞짠횞혮횞혷횞혫횞혲횞징횞혱횞혮횞짢 횞혲횞짤횞혮횞혩 횞혩횞짤횞혩횞혮횞짖 횞혬횞혩횞혨 횞짖횞혶 횞짤횞짧횞혲 횞혱횞혴횞혻횞혲횞혮횞짧.
- 횞혨횞혰횞짧 횞짢횞혪횞혲횞혵횞혬 횞혩횞혲횞혮횞혶 횞짤횞혻횞혲, 횞혮횞혩횞혲횞혮횞혶 횞혰횞혷횞혲횞짤횞혲 횞혲횞혮횞혶 횞혬횞짖횞짝횞혷횞혨횞혮횞짧 횞짧횞혮횞혴횞혻횞혲횞짧 횞혷횞혲횞혮횞혰횞혫횞짧 횞짤횞혵 횞짤횞짖횞혬 횞혩-835.
- 횞짧횞혮횞혫횞혬 횞짢횞혩횞혬.
- 횞혴횞혵 횞혬횞혴횞혩횞혮횞혫, 횞혴횞혵 횞혬횞혴횞혩횞혮횞혫.
- 횞혷횞혻횞혲횞혨횞혻횞혲횞혨횞짠횞혲.